Okay, let's see what
Bueno vamos a ver lo de
Shakira's doing, Javi. You can hear me better now, of
Shakira Javi ya se te escucha mejor
course. Maribel, but I just wouldn't stop. Oh,
claro Maribel pero es que no paraba Ah
look, what happened over the weekend, looking on the
mira lo del fin de semana viendo el lado
bright side, it also helped me a little bit
bueno me ha servido también un poquito
to disconnect and to force myself to
para desconectar y para obligarme a
stop working, force myself to stop, it's
parar de trabajar obligarme a parar que
not a problem to stop, trita. You have
tampoco pasa nada por parar trita tienes
a lot to put on, late. There's a lot of
mucho para poner tardía hay mucho tema
salt issues. It would be a
de sal sería de
honor for the kids. It's the naughty hour.
señoría la chavalería es la hora golfa
Today. Not today. The kids are here.
Hoy No hoy la chavalería
When I'm done here with you. I don't
aquí cuando termine aquí con ustedes no
know how long we'll be here. However long it takes, I'll
sé cuánto tiempo estaremos lo que
go over there. Because today
tardemos me iré para allá Porque hoy
I want to be here at night. Today I want to
quiero estar por la noche con hoy quiero
sleep with the
dormir con el
kid. Let's see what
niño vamos a ver lo de Shakira vale
Shakira's doing. Okay, let's see what Shakira's doing. If I'm not
vamos a ver lo de Shakira que si no me
mistaken, from what I've heard on
equivoco por lo que sí he escuchado en
the radio, the Shakira thing. Let's see. I do
la radio el tema Shakira Es que a ver yo
n't know if you'll agree with me.
no sé si estaré de acuerdo conmigo
No, but not with me. Where do you think the
No pero no a mí a donde tienen que los
Ikea hot dogs are? They're dying. Javi. No, I do
perritos de Ikea están en muerte Javi no
n't like them. They're made of plastic.
no me gustan Son son de plástico no
They're not that great. Let's see. You can
están muo a ver lo que sí podéis
each treat me to a hot dog if
invitarme cada uno a un perrito si
you want. Okay, you have the button down there.
queréis vale por ahí abajo tenéis el
of Super chat okay if you want to
botón de Super chat vale si queréis
invite me a hot dog there you have the
invitarme un perrito ahí tenéis el botón
Super chat button I don't know if it cost 1 euro the
de Super chat No sé si valía 1 eur el
hot dog eh or two I don't remember and I'll eat
perrito eh o dos no me acuerdo y me como
a hot dog here then in a while
un perrito aquí luego dentro de un rato
okay or I'll go out to get the hot dog at the kiosk
vale o salgo a por el perrito al kiosco
eh the Shakira issue Well I think
eh el tema Shakira Pues yo creo que
Shakira had it complicated eh she says
Shakira lo tenía complicado eh ella dice
that she has reached an agreement because the
que ha llegado al acuerdo pues porque el
issue is finalized since it is also good
tema se finaliza ya que también es bueno
eh I mean because I eh And
eh o sea porque yo eh Y esto lo dicen
many lawyers often say this that a good
muchos abogados muchas veces que un buen
agreement is also a victory
acuerdo también es una victoria alguna
sometimes okay No but it is that he has pleaded
vez vale No pero es que se ha declarado
guilty he has acknowledged the facts Well
culpable ha reconocido los hechos Bueno
then he has acknowledged the facts if
pues ha reconocido los hechos si es que
none of us are perfect yes it is that we all
ninguno somos perfectos si es que todos
make some mistakes then Hey to
cometemos algún error entonces Oye que
acknowledge the facts But well settle the
reconocer los hechos Pero bueno sanja el
issue and tomorrow this issue will be over it is not
tema y mañana se acabó este tema no está
bad I have also done it on some
mal yo también lo he hecho en alguna
occasions reach an agreement and the issue is
ocasión llegar acuerdo y el tema se
settled and to hell with it and it is better than
sanja y a tomar por culo y es mejor que
being 10 years 6 years 8 years and come on
estar 10 años 6 años 8 años y venga
letting the lawyer go and now you have to
soltarle al abogado y ahora tienes que
go there and now you have to go
ir para allá y ahora tienes que ir para
here and Ah it is written Ah you know  what I
acá y Ah está escrito Ah sabes lo que te
always tell you asking what a shame says
digo siempre pidiendo qué vergüenza dice
purin family forgive me forgive me puri
purin familia perdonarme perdóname puri
forgive me puri family that puri has been
perdóname puri familia que puri se ha
offended I did not invite myself to any hot dog
ofendido no me invité a ningún perrito
but puri if you are not even a member but
pero puri si no eres Ni miembro pero
puri if you are not even a member that you are going to
puri si no eres Ni miembro que te vas a
man if it occurred to me that you are
hombre si me di a mí que te estás
spending the euro a month well it's okay
gastando el euro al mes pues está bien
that you complain [ __ ] I'm fed up I'm fed up
que te quejes [__] estoy harta estoy
on top of that I pay you the euro a month
harta encima que te pago el euro al mes
but that's why you are not even a member
pero por es que no eres Ni miembro
why do you complain if it's not yours
porque te quejas si tuyo no
Ah okay Mimi remind me that we watch the
Ah vale Mimi recuérdamelo que veamos los
Dandy Lucas Yeah now remind me we'll
Dandy Lucas Sí ahora recuérdamelo lo
see the wear and tear and such what
vemos lo vemos el desgaste y tal lo que
happens is that it's not over eh Because I
pasa es que no ha terminado eh Porque
think she has two more procedures what
creo que tiene dos procedimientos más lo
happens is that it is true that the
que pasa que sí que es verdad que los
other two procedures is the
otros dos procedimientos es la
claim of pacha at the moment it does not enter
reclamación de pacha de momento no entra
into criminal law Because still She is not
en penal Porque todavía Ella no se está
refusing to pay or anything like that
negando a pagar ni nada por el estilo
So she will pay it too and outside it's that
Entonces lo pagará también y fuera es
in the end also
que al final también
eh with the famous something happens that no that they don't understand
eh con los famosos pasa una cosa que no
okay
que no se entera vale
eh that they don't understand and it's something that the [ __ ]
eh que no se enteran y es algo que [__]
all the self-employed us  It's very
a todos los autónomos nos da mucho
annoying, okay, self-employed companies,
coraje vale autónomos sociedades a todo
not everyone who contributes in Spain, and the
el que cotice en España no y es que el
tax issue in Spain,
tema fiscal en España
I
el tema fiscal en España yo lo yo lo
consider it legal theft,
considero un robo
legal theft Javi will comment, I'm
legal Javi comentará
not going to say what I was going to
la no voy a decir lo que iba a
say, legal theft, that is, here are the
decir un robo legal o sea aquí los
percentages that you have to pay, eh
porcentajes que tienes que pagar eh
No, it doesn't make sense, it doesn't make sense, I
No no tiene sentido no tiene sentido o
mean, I'm not telling you not to pay
sea yo no te digo que que no pagues
taxes because I completely
impuestos porque yo estoy Completamente
agree that everyone should pay what they
de acuerdo en que todos paguen lo que
have to pay and that each one pays
tengan que pagar y que cada uno pague en
based on what they earn, of course, but
función a lo que cobre por supuesto pero
man, you can't give me 50%,
hombre Tú no me puedes poner un 50% un
47%, I think 25% is fine, no,
47 por Yo creo que un 25% está bien no
25, damn, the one who earns 2,000 is not going to pay you the same
25 [__] No te va a pagar lo mismo el que
as the one who earns
cobre 2000 que el que cobre
3,000, but of course, a person like this who
3000 pero claro una persona de estas que
beats you, like it happens with many of
te gana como pasa con muchos youtubers
these big youtubers, who earn
de estos de los grandes no que cobran
200,000 a month, well, of course, you're
200000 al mes Pues claro tú le estás
taking away 1,000, you know, not 150, but well,
quitando 1000 sabes no 150 Pero bueno t
you're taking away more than 100,000  per
tú le estás quitando más de 100000 al
month Of course, but of course the issue is that
mes Pues claro pero claro el tema es que
you leave Spain. Don't pay taxes here, you
te vayas de España No cotices aquí tú te
can go pay taxes wherever you want.
puedes ir a tributar donde te dé la gana
If you're a singer, if you're a YouTuber,
si eres un cantante si eres un youtuber
yeah, I don't know what, you can go pay
sies no sé qué tú te puedes ir a
taxes wherever you want, but if you stay
tributar donde quieras pero si te quedas
in Spain, you stay with the conditions
en España te quedas con las condiciones
of Spain. I mean,
de España
me, for example, forgive me for
o sea yo por ejemplo a mí perdonadme por
the expression but it pisses me off a lot, it pisses me off a
la expresión pero me jode muchísimo me
lot, it pisses me off and it makes me indignant and I
jode muchísimo me cabrea y me indigna y
will complain and I will cry a lot, but the thing is that
me quejaré y Lloraré muchísimo pero es
I want to stay in Spain to live. So
que me quiero quedar en España a vivir
if I want to stay to live, what you ca
Entonces si me quiero quedar a vivir lo
n't do are shady deals and things,
que no puedes hacer chanchullos y cosas
you know, you have to do what there
sabes tienes que hacer lo que
is in the way that comes out best for you, that's
hay de la manera que mejor te salga ya
it, but not to me it
está pero no a m a
's no ro puri. Sorry ro puri.
tienza es no ro puri Perdona ro puri
Sorry puri puri, sorry honey to ro
Perdona puri puri perdona cariño a ro
puri. Sorry r I'll pay you
puri Perdona r luego te lo
back later, it says men chuca if you don't reach a
devuelvo dice men chuca si no llegaras a
certain amount you don't pay 45
cierta cantidad no pagas el 45
for.  men chuca but any person
por. men chuca pero cualquier persona
who has a business that is doing more or
que tenga un negocio que le vaya más o
less well if they reach that certain
menos bien si llega a esa cierta
amount in a few months eh I mean if you
cantidad en poco meses eh o sea si tú
have a bar a bar a
tienes un bar un bar
beauty shop a
un una tienda estética un negocio de
construction business no Gisela don't cook it no no no eh
obras no Gisela no guisela no no no eh
well for the hot dog hot dog don't
bueno para el perrito perrito caliente
cook it hot dogs I won't give it back to you
no guisela perritos no te lo devuelvo
then cook it puri Sorry eh Sorry
luego guisela puri Perdona eh Perdona
puri don't be offended marilu those are a
puri no se ofenda usted marilu esos son
lot of hot dogs puri pu that that's delit
muchos perritos puri pu eso eso es delit
less Javi pu And I'm sorry Well if you
de menos Javi pu Y lo siento Bueno si le
ask puri for forgiveness okay puri Sorry puri are you
pedís perdón a puri vale puri Perdona
still
puri sigues por
there no Raquel Raquel no no no puri sorry
ahí no Raquel Raquel no no no puri
Sorry puri sorry eh Sorry puri
eh Perdona puri perdona eh Perdona
queen Do you think you have to
reina Es que ustedes os creéis que hay
earn millions so that they can
que cobrar millonadas para que te
take so much from you let's see if it
lleguen a quitar muchísimo a ver si que
's true that maybe the
es verdad que a lo mejor el
maximum
máximo
eh the maximum maybe it is a lot of
eh el máximo a lo mejor sí que es mucho
money but it doesn't have to be the
dinero pero no tiene por qué ser el
maximum for it to be a lot Okay come on Well
máximo para que sea mucho Bueno venga
maybe  They don't take away the 47 from you. Well,
Pues a lo mejor no te quitan el 47 Bueno
maybe they take away
pues a lo mejor te quitan un
40. Maybe they take away
40 A lo mejor te quitan un
40. I don't remember exactly
40 no me acuerdo exactamente de memoria
how much the amounts are, but
Cuánto son las cantidades pero una
maybe a person and I have a business, maybe
persona a lo mejor y yo un negocio a lo
a bar, a business
mejor un bar un negocio que un negocio
that's doing well, a business that's one
que te vaya bien un negocio que que sea
of those for aesthetics,
de estos de estética
eh, or for construction, it's worth it. A person who has
eh o de obras vale una persona que tenga
a business that's doing well, or
un negocio que que vaya bien vale o
has a couple of businesses that are doing well, and maybe
tenga un par de negocios que vaya bien y
between the two
a lo mejor ingresa entre los dos
businesses they earn
negocios
5,000. You understand, that one is paying you, not
5000 me entiendes ese está pagándote no
exactly half, but that one is
la mitad exactamente pero ese te está
paying you, that one is paying you a lot.
pagando ese te está pagando muchísimo
Of course, you say, Oh, but it's that, of
Claro tú dices Ay pero es que es que
course, if you earn 40,000 a year, if
claro es que si tú cobras 40.000 al año
you keep 20, you're fine, of
con a que te quedes con 20 vas bien
course, and there are people who live with, you
claro y hay gente que vive con
know, you adapt to what they have.
con sabes tú te adapt a lo que tiene
But man, if you're earning
pero hombre pero si tú estás ganando
this much and your business is generating this much,
esto y tu negocio está generando esto
why do you have to give half to the
por qué le tienes que dar la mitad al
state? It doesn't make sense. But
estado es que no tiene sentido Pero
anyway, the
bueno de todas maneras la
protest, the protest, if you're in
protesta la protesta que si estás en
Spain, Maribel, Maribel, a kiss,
España Maribel Maribel un beso
queen, for the puppy.  Grandpa
reina para el perrito perrito
a kiss Maribel
Abuelo un beso Maribel
sweetheart if you stay in
corazón que si te quedas en
Spain that's what there is what you can't
España es lo que hay lo que no puedes
oppose to
oponerte a
pay it mine's puppy a kiss
pagarlo el perrito de el mío un beso
Thank you but Puri has gone Puri has
Gracias pero puri se ha ido puri se ha
gone Puri
ido puri
demonstrate something is
manifiéstate algo
prohibited to work eh or rather it is prohibited to
prohibido trabajar eh o sea prohibido
charge for working Puri I have been 4
cobrar por trabajar puri que llevo 4
days without doing anything let me recover
días sin hac nada déjame que recupere
something Total that has reached an agreement
algo Total que ha llegado a un acuerdo
in which in the end he pays what he
en el que al final paga lo que
owes In other words, in the end he will pay it in the
debe O sea al final lo va a pagar al
end he will pay it plus a fine so that there is no
final lo paga más una multa para que no
jail time The Treasury
haya cárcel Hacienda
normally The Treasury
normalmente Hacienda
normally usually reaches agreements with
normalmente suele llegar acuerdos con
these people so that they prefer that you
esta gente para que o sea prefieren que
pay that you pay than that you go to
paguen que pagues a que entres en la
jail or something like that what does it matter to them that you
cárcel o algo así de queé les vale que
go to jail you pay and that's it
entres en la cárcel pagas y ya
I produce I want to earn well and for the
está yo s produzco Quiero ganar bien y
Treasury to charge me as what they don't
que Hacienda me cobre como lo que no
produce I don't understand come on but what is what I'm
produzcan no entiendo jala pero que es
telling you I mean if you get
lo que te digo O sea si tú consigues en
a lot of business in your business it
tu negocio trabajando mucho negocio te
generates 4000 5000 a month what happens because you
genere 4000 5000 al mes qué pasa porque
have to give a lot of Treasury Damn  you
le tienes que dar mucho Hacienda [__] tú
give him your part which corresponds to a
le das tu parte que corresponde un
percentage of course the problem is that it is not
porcentaje claro el problema es que
necessary if it is not that you
además no hace falta si ya no es que te
sio The problem is that it is not necessary so much
lo sio El problema es que no hace falta
that then the money is wasted
tanto que luego se desperdicia el dinero
eh you find the corruption that there is
eh te encuentras la corrupción que hay
with the money and all the things there
con el dinero y todas las cosas ahí
then you say this is the problem
entonces ya dices tú este es el problema
that gets on every
que te toca las narices cada
Spaniard's nerves but not me where do they have to
español pero no a mí a donde tienen que
for broccoli
para brocoli
Sorry a kiss beautiful Raquel if he still has a
Perdón un beso guapísima Raquel si le
criminal record Well of course he
quedan antecedentes penales Pues claro
suspends the sentence, I mean it is supposed that
suspende la pena o sea se supone que en
instead of 8 years they sentence him to 3 years but he
vez de 8 años le condenan a 3 años pero
also does not enter because Well then he pays the
tampoco entra porque Bueno pues paga la
fine I don't know what I don't know how much he knows the
murta no sé qué no sé cuánto conoce los
facts and he conforms to the new
hechos y se conforma con las nuevas
sentences that have been requested of him, thus he
penas que le han sido solicitadas así
avoided jail and settled one of his
esquivaba la cárcel y zaba una de sus
pending accounts with the
cuentas pendientes con la justicia
Spanish justice system, admitted to tax fraud
española admitido el fraude fiscal
committed between 2012 and 2014 upon leaving
cometido entre 2012 y 2014 a la salida
the Barcelona court, his lawyer
de la corte de Barcelona su abogada
assured that she was prepared to win the
aseguraba estar preparada para ganar el
trial but they asked for 8 years, man, I mean 8
juicio pero le pedían 8 años tío o sea 8
years is an outrage
años es una barbaridad
No, well he already won in those two years to
No pues ya ganó en esos dos años para
pay  That millionaire, that man, let's see,
pagar esa millonaria esa hombre a ver
we're talking about Shakira, Leonia
estamos hablando de Shakira leonia
Shakira. How many millions can she earn? I put together,
Shakira Cuántos millones puede ganar
but they were asking for that for 8 years, to show off, man, so
pero 8 años le pedían eso para afar tío
you can [ __ ] yourself, so you can pay for it straight away.
para que te cagues para que lo pagues
Eh, yes or
por huevo Eh sí o
yes, how are they, eh, Xavi Alonso, Sito, boom,
sí cómo son eh Xavi Alonso Sito
Dani, alve, they've won lately,
pum Dani alve han ganado últimamente
shallow. The Treasury, yes, you can win it, of course, let's
playos Hacienda sí lo puedes ganar claro
see if you've done things right, you win it.
a ver si tú tienes las cosas bien hechas
There are many times when they might make mistakes. There are many times when they make
equivocan hay muchas veces que ellos se
mistakes, but of course, you have to
equivocan pero pero claro tienes que
have the desire to go all the way. And
tener ganas de llegar hasta el final Y
such. But I think that in Shakira's case,
tal Pero yo creo que en el caso de
it was difficult, eh. Because
Shakira lo tenía difícil eh Porque
what Shakira wants to claim is,
Shakira lo que quiere alegar es
eh, what can I tell you? No, that she, in that, that
eh qué te digo yo que no que ella en ese
her tax residence in those years
que ella su residencia fiscal esos años
was in the islands, I don't know what, that.
estaba en las islas no sé qué eso
How did she know that
Cómo
the will prevailed? The
sababa que ha primado la voluntad el
agreement reached contemplates the payment of
acuerdo alcanzado contempla el pago de
around 8 and a half million
alrededor de 8 millones y medio de
dollars, eight of which come from a
dólares ocho de ellos proceden de una
fine of 50% of the outstanding installments
multa del 50% de las cuotas adeudadas
that had already been previously repaid.
que ya habían sido restituidas con
The amount  remaining avoids
anterioridad La cantidad restante evita
the sentence of 3 years in prison for this
la condena de 3 años de cárcel para este
judge it is a fair agreement It
magistrado se trata de un pacto justo Me
seems to me a reasonable agreement because
parece un acuerdo razonable porque En
Ultimately it faces the entire debt
definitiva hace frente a toda la deuda
eh of That is if in the end
eh de Ya está si es que al final al a la
what interests the treasury is to collect
hacienda lo que le interesa es ingresar
money Pantoja 2 years and went to
dinero la Pantoja 2 años y entró en la
jail is that what happened to Pantoja I do not know
cárcel es que lo de la Pantoja yo no sé
if someone could explain to me why
si alguien me sabría explicar porque la
Pantoja went to jail is that I do not know what happened
Pantoja entró en la cárcel es que yo lo
to Pantoja if it is also that Pantoja No
de la Pantoja no lo si es que además la
I do not know why Pantoja did not suspend the sentence I do not understand it is that Pantoja's
No yo no s yo no sé por qué la Pantoja
was not
entiendo es que lo de la Pantoja no era
to enter it can be suspended I do not know
para entrar se puede suspender no sé el
why the
Por qué la
truth I do not know why I do not know
verdad no sé el Por
if it is the type of
qué no sé si es el tipo de
crime the way to
delito la forma de
do it I do not know the truth I do not know
hacerlo No lo sé la verdad no sé el por
why you say
qué tú dices
exemplary
ejemplarizante
Of course but and Shakira is not more
Claro pero y Shakira no es más
famous I do not know why the truth a year
famosa no sé el Por qué la verdad un año
and 3
y 3
months but no but I do not
meses pero no pero no
understand why she did not pay because she did
entiendo porque no pagó
not accept the crime because she did not pay
porque no aceptó el delito porque no
whatever
pagó lo que
was defrauded and also will pay some
sea defraudada y además Abonará unas
fines for  avoid prison
multas para eludir la prisión con lo
which seems reasonable to me, also taking
cual me parece algo razonable además
into account her high
teniendo en cuenta su alta capacidad
economic capacity, until today Sakir had
económica hasta hoy sakir había
failed in several attempts to reach
fracasado en varios intentos de llegar a
an agreement with the authorities, the pact
un acuerdo con las autoridades el pacto
ensures that she is free from the impact that
asegura ella la libra del impacto que
her media exposure would have and a
tendría su exposición mediática y un
trial that would drag on for months, she
juicio que se alargaría durante meses lo
said a statement in which Sur also
ha dicho comunicado en el que además Sur
stated that she had made the decision
rayaba que había tomado la decisión
mainly thinking about her
principalmente pensando en su
stability and that of her children and her
estabilidad y en la de sus hijos y en su
professional career, the singer
carrera profesional la cantante Tiene
still has two pending cases in Spain,
todavía dos causas pendientes en España
my children have
mis hijos me lo han
asked me to, I think that's a bit of an
pedido yo eso creo que es un poco un
argument, she always always says no, my
argumento siempre siempre dice no mis
children tell me with the song Bizarr, she
hijos me la con la canción de bizarr
also said it, it's not that she wrote the song
también lo dijo No es que la canción de
Bizarr because my children have
bizarra la ha hecho porque mis hijos me
asked me to,
pedido
but she doesn't
de la cera pero ella no habla fíjate ni
even talk about that or the public ridicule,
siquiera de eso ni del escarnio público
she talks about prioritizing her time on her
ella habla de priorizar su tiempo en su
career and her children, I
carrera y en sus hijos o
mean, but if it's that anyway you
sea pero si es que de todas maneras tú
don't spend your time, let's see if if you
el tiempo no lo empleas a ver si si tú
have this issue, I mean, what was it taking away from
tienes este tema o sea en qué le quitaba
her children's time if she hadn't
el tiempo de sus hijos el que no hubiera
accepted an agreement
aceptado un acuerdo
in having to go to Spain, I don't know what, no  I know
en tener que ir a España no sé qué no sé
how much maybe I don't know what you mean
cuánto a lo mejor no sé a qué se refiere
by that the truth is if a person who
con eso la verdad si una persona que
always I don't know the truth that always has to
siempre no sé la verdad que siempre
be on tour that always has to be
tiene que estar de gira que siempre
up and down I don't
tiene que estar para arriba para abajo
understand the
no entiendo la
truth is that it's not that it has nothing to
verdad es que no es que no tiene nada
do with it, let's see you've reached an agreement
que ver a ver has llegado a un acuerdo
because it's the best you can do and you
porque es lo mejor que puedes hacer y te
get it over with It
lo quitas de encima Es que a mí me
seems fine to me, I mean if you have the
parece bien o sea si tienes la
opportunity for an agreement why
oportunidad de un acuerdo para qué
continue with an issue from a
continúa con un tema de hace una
decade ago yes I know that a document is being recorded
década sí sé que está grabando un
in fact some of the scenes today
de hecho algunas de las escenas de hoy
were for the
era para para el
documentary it doesn't matter what they tell him if
documental da igual que le digan si se
the wax is done if it is deiled if they p the
hace la cera si se deila si se p las
mech the point one speaks of avoiding the
mech el punto un habla de evitar así el
impact of the media exposure and the
impacto de la exposición mediática y el
time of the trial that in many occasions
tiempo de juicio que en muchas ocasiones
is of a length let's see there was also
es de una longitud a ver también había
a
una
move And it is that they had called like
movida Y es que habían llamado como a
more than 100
más de 100
witnesses says I'm going to give my example of
testigos dice voy a poner mi ejemplo de
233 that he pays I have 100 left of
233 que paga a mí me quedan 100
course Yes yes there are worse examples jalsa there are
claro Sí sí hay ejemplos peores jalsa
strong examples
hay ejemplos fuertes
eh And it's not that but you say Well
eh Y no es eso sino que tú dices Bueno
come on but then you see yourself in  that they
venga va pero luego te ves en que se
spend the money many times and this is why it is not
gastan el dinero muchas veces y de esto
necessary so much if the money
es que no hace falta tanto si el dinero
were managed
se gestionará
well you know exhausting is point number
bien sabes extenuante es el punto número
one avoiding the impact of
uno evitar el impacto de exposición
media exposure to me it seems enough that this
mediática a me parece suf que que eso
demonstrates the fiscal terror that reigns in
demuestra el terror fiscal que reina en
Spain they have no shame they have no
España no tienen vergüenza no tienen
dignity I mean I am from the
dignidad o sea yo soy de la agencia
tax agency I would be ashamed if
tributaria me daría vergüenza que
someone published that they do it out of
alguien publicara que lo hace por por
fear
miedo
eh they were there I mean they had called
eh iban ahí o sea habían llamado a
more than a hundred and some
declarar a más de ciento y pico de
people to testify so that they would talk about her like
persona para que hablaran de ella en
people who do her makeup people from the
plan a gente que la maquilla a gente del
children's school out of fear you know it is a
niños por miedo sabes que es un
statement Federico that includes
comunicado Federico que incluye
quotes from the singer herself
entrecomillados de la propia cantante
something that we are not
cosa que a la que no estamos
used to Open quotes he says I
acostumbrados Abre comillas dice me
felt ready to face a trial
sentía lista para enfrentarme un juicio
and defend my innocence my lawyers
y defender mi inocencia mis abogados
were convinced that we had a
estaban convencidos de que teníamos un
winning trial however I mean he says what he
juicio ganador sin embarg o sea
says that does not add up to me he
dice eso que dice que a mí no me cuadra
says no my lawyers knew that it was a
dice no mis abogados sabían que era un
trial won But well we did not
juicio ganado Pero bueno no teníamos
want more time to pass to see that
ganas que pasara más tiempo a ver eso
either
tampoco
if it is a trial
si es un juicio
won How are you not going to go ahead I
ganado Cómo no vas a tirar para adante O
mean if it is a trial  won if your
sea si es un juicio ganado si tus
lawyers think it's a won trial
abogados piensan que es un juicio